# **URE MILIA**

Fullstack Engineer



33 years old



I have 5 years of experience as a fullstack engineer.

I had the opportunity to contribute to more than 50 projects (web and mobile applications).

I am particularly interested by the **front-end** part of development and would like to work with Vue.js, React or Angular.

I am available for immediate employment (or before July 2024), as a remote worker (or 2 days/week on site at Toulouse).

## WORK EXPERIENCES

#### Web and mobile developer

Bleu122 | 2017 - 2022 (5 ans et 4 mois)

Bleu122 creates web and mobile applications from scratch. I joined the company as an intern. Following this intership I've been hired as a web and mobile developer, then as lead web developer.

I had the opportunity to work on more than 50 projects for various types of companies (veterinary clinic, aeronautics, podcasts publisher...)

I have been involved at all levels of the life cycle of an IT project, from the first meeting with a new client to publishing the application online or on applications stores.

I had the chance to see the company grow from 4 to 17 employees. I helped support this growth and organize the team as a member of the management committee.

Some projects I worked on:

- Pica Grails / jQuery Web application to manage collisions between planes and animals for French Civil Aviation Authority.
- PriceInsight Grails / jQuery Web application to collect and analyse prices from concurrence for TotalEnergies.
- Omitzuka Grails / Vue.js Mobile application to bet (for free) on sports with friends.

#### Webmarketing and project management

Ctouvert | 2015 - 2016 (1 an et 2 mois)

Ctoutvert is a company offering e-commerce solutions for tourism, including a software for online reservation used by numerous campsites across Europe.

I worked on different subjects: project management, SEO, SEA (Adwords), social networks, newsletters...

I worked with a team of approximately 20 developers and this collaboration that made me want to become one myself!

#### CERTIFICATIONS

#### **Build a Modern Computer from First Principles: Nand to Tetris**

Coursera (HUJI) | 2023

The intent of this course is to build a fully functional computer (to play Tetris on!).

My motivation for taking this class was to gain a deeper understanding of all the layers that constitute a modern computer.

Before taking this course I developed programs running on a magic and mysterious box. Now it's still magic but not that mysterious anymore  $\bigcirc$ 

- My Github page with all the completed projects
- Coursera Certifications : part 1 part 2

## LANGUAGES

French - Native

English - B2 (Professional) 1 year of practice in Australia

#### TECHNOLOGIES

JavaScript - jQuery, Vue.js

PHP - Wordpress, Laravel, Symfony

Java - Groovy, Grails

iOS - Swift

SQL/HQL and database conception

Others - I am a quick learner and always curious to get to work with new tools!

#### **EDUCATION**

Mobile & web development Simplon.co 2016 - 2017

Master 2 Digital Communication

UCO Angers / Toulouse 3 UPS 2009 - 2015

